=Side Story Of Fox Volant= (Adapted from Jin Yong's novel)
= قصة جانبية لـ Fox Volant = (مقتبس من رواية Jin Yong)
=Episode 33=
= الحلقة 33 =
(Huaquan Sect)
(طائفة هوا تشيوان)
It seems
يبدو
she's been cleansed of the poison.
لقد تم تطهيرها من السم.
That is great.
هذا عظيم.
Sister Ma is going to get well soon,
ستتحسن الأخت ما قريبًا ،
am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Don't celebrate too soon.
لا تحتفل في وقت مبكر جدا.
The poison is gone,
ذهب السم ،
but her heart meridian was damaged.
لكن خط زوال قلبها تضرر.
We need you to channel your qi to her
نحن بحاجة منك لتوجيه qi الخاص بك إليها
and help her recover vitality.
ومساعدتها على استعادة حيويتها.
That's easy.
هذا سهل.
I can do it now.
أستطيع أن أفعلها الآن.
That can wait.
يمكن أن ينتظر.
Xiaomei, prepare the medicine.
Xiaomei ، تحضير الدواء.
Yes.
نعم.
You can channel your qi to her
يمكنك توجيه qi لها
after she's taken medicine.
بعد أن أخذت الدواء.
Old Master.
فنان قديم.
Is the wedding gown ready?
هل ثوب الزفاف جاهز؟
Has she tried it on?
هل حاولت ذلك؟
Guinong.
جينونج.
I've been thinking.
كنت افكر.
I'm still concerned.
ما زلت قلقة.
Am I lacking something?
هل ينقصني شيء؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
I'll make it up to you.
سوف أعوضها لك.
But promise me
لكن وعدني
you're never leaving me again.
أنت لا تتركني مرة أخرى.
I know you love me.
انا اعرف انك تحبني.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
أنا أقدر تفكيرك.
Since we are going to marry each other,
بما أننا سوف نتزوج بعضنا البعض ،
could you promise me one thing?
هل يمكن أن تعدني بشيء واحد؟
Have I ever said no to you?
هل قلت لك لا من قبل؟
As you know,
وانت عارف،
I've hated the conflicts and fighting in the martial arts world.
لقد كرهت الصراعات والقتال في عالم فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
My father
والدي
once had the Cold Moon Saber forged
ذات مرة تم تزوير صابر القمر البارد
to help him rise to power.
لمساعدته في الوصول إلى السلطة.
But he was ambushed
لكنه تعرض لكمين
and died in a foreign land.
ومات في أرض أجنبية.
I met Miao Renfeng because of this blade
لقد قابلت مياو رينفينج بسبب هذا النصل
and married him.
وتزوجته.
Thankfully, the blade has been hidden in a snow cave.
لحسن الحظ ، تم إخفاء النصل في كهف ثلجي.
Otherwise, there would be yet another bloodshed.
وإلا فسيحدث إراقة دماء أخرى.
But I get it now.
لكنني فهمت الآن.
As long as you're in the martial arts world,
طالما أنك في عالم فنون الدفاع عن النفس ،
conflicts are inevitable.
الصراعات لا مفر منها.
After we are married,
بعد أن نتزوج ،
I want both of us to leave that life behind and lead a quiet life,
أريد أن يترك كلانا تلك الحياة وراءنا ونعيش حياة هادئة ،
never to get involved again.
لا تتدخل مرة أخرى.
Guinong?
جينونج؟
When you wanted me to come back,
عندما أردت مني أن أعود ،
you said you'd give up anything for me.
قلت أنك ستتخلى عن أي شيء من أجلي.
Do you not remember that?
ألا تتذكر ذلك؟
I didn't think
لم أفكر
your wish
امنيتك
was the same as my late father's.
كان هو نفسه والدي الراحل.
Do you know how I got my name?
هل تعلم كيف حصلت على اسمي؟
My father spent his entire life in bloodshed.
قضى والدي حياته كلها في إراقة الدماء.
He grew tired of the life
لقد سئم الحياة
of blades and killings.
من ريش وقتل.
He used his entire life
لقد استخدم حياته كلها
to establish the foundation for our family.
لتأسيس الأساس لعائلتنا.
He wanted our future generation
أراد جيل المستقبل
to retreat to a peaceful farming life.
للتراجع إلى حياة زراعية سلمية.
Does that mean
هل هذا يعني
you agree?
انت موافق
I agree.
أنا موافق.
I'll go to the capital
سأذهب إلى العاصمة
and take part in the World's Sect Leaders Gathering.
والمشاركة في تجمع قادة الطوائف في العالم.
After that, I'll leave that life behind.
بعد ذلك ، سأترك تلك الحياة ورائي.
It can't be helped.
فإنه لا يمكن أن تكون ساعدت.
If I didn't attend it after getting the Jade Dragon Cup,
إذا لم أحضره بعد حصولي على كأس Jade Dragon ،
the Imperial Court
المحكمة الامبراطورية
will hold the entire Tianlong Sect accountable.
سوف يحاسب طائفة تيانلونغ بأكملها.
I understand.
أفهم.
After your business there is done,
بعد الانتهاء من عملك هناك ،
we'll get married.
سوف نتزوج.
And after we get married,
وبعد أن نتزوج ،
I'll take you to wherever you want.
سآخذك إلى أي مكان تريده.
Let me have a good look at you.
اسمحوا لي أن ألقي نظرة فاحصة عليك.
You look gorgeous in it.
تبدو رائعًا فيه.
Gorgeous.
خلاب.
Fei,
فاي ،
this is your second time breaking into the manor.
هذه هي المرة الثانية التي تقتحم فيها القصر.
You're a wanted fugitive in the city.
أنت هارب مطلوب في المدينة.
I only ask that you stop being so rash.
أنا فقط أطلب منك أن تتوقف عن كونك متهورًا جدًا.
Yes.
نعم.
I'll do as you say.
سأفعل كما تقول.
No more rash decisions.
لا مزيد من القرارات المتهورة.
You agree without hesitation,
أنت توافق دون تردد ،
but you always break your promise in the end.
لكنك تخلف دائمًا بوعدك في النهاية.
Well, let's do a pinky swear.
حسنًا ، لنقم بأداء قسم الخنصر.
If I ever get too reckless
إذا أصبحت متهورًا جدًا
or too rash,
أو طفح جلدي شديد ،
show your pinky finger.
تظهر إصبعك الخنصر.
That will remind me.
سوف يذكرني ذلك.
Very well, we'll do just that.
حسنًا ، سنفعل ذلك بالضبط.
Deal.
صفقة.
By the way, Lingsu.
بالمناسبة ، Lingsu.
There is something I must discuss with you.
هناك شيء يجب أن أناقشه معك.
Fu Kang'an sent an officer
أرسل فو كانجان ضابطا
to confirm the headcount for the World's Sect Leaders Gathering.
لتأكيد عدد العاملين في تجمع قادة الطوائف في العالم.
I want you and Ji Xiaofeng to come with me.
أريدك أنت وجي شياو فنغ أن تأتي معي.
Must you attend that gathering?
هل يجب أن تحضر هذا التجمع؟
I promised Ji Xiaofeng
لقد وعدت جي شياو فنغ
I'd win
سأفوز
a cup for the Huaquan Sect
كوب لطائفة Huaquan
to redeem their honor.
لتخليص شرفهم.
Besides,
بجانب،
Feng Tiannan will certainly show up there.
بالتأكيد سيظهر فنغ تيانان هناك.
I can settle the score with him there.
يمكنني تسوية النتيجة معه هناك.
But you're a wanted fugitive.
لكنك هارب مطلوب.
If you go there again,
إذا ذهبت إلى هناك مرة أخرى ،
you might not make it out.
قد لا تفعل ذلك.
I have you, a master of disguise.
لدي أنت ، سيد التنكر.
They won't notice it.
لن يلاحظوا ذلك.
Besides,
بجانب،
don't you want to learn more
لا تريد معرفة المزيد
about the heartbreak grass?
عن عشب حسرة؟
This is a gathering of heroes and warriors.
هذا تجمع للأبطال والمحاربين.
You will find some new information there.
ستجد بعض المعلومات الجديدة هناك.
Are these
هل هؤلاء
your only reasons to attend the gathering?
أسبابك الوحيدة لحضور الاجتماع؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Young Lady Yuan will be there as well,
السيدة الشابة "يوان" ستكون هناك أيضًا ،
right?
الصحيح؟
Ziyi?
ما هم؟
Probably.
المحتمل.
Don't you want to get some answers
لا تريد الحصول على بعض الإجابات
and clear your doubts?
ويبيّن شكوكك؟
I...
أنا...
Of course I'd want that.
بالطبع أريد ذلك.
Actually, I managed to rescue the boys
في الواقع ، تمكنت من إنقاذ الأولاد
because Ziyi helped out.
لأن زيي ساعد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
How did she help?
كيف ساعدت؟
She was on guard duty at the consort's house.
كانت تقوم بواجب الحراسة في منزل القرين.
She recognized me,
لقد تعرفت علي ،
but she didn't expose me.
لكنها لم تكشف لي.
I ran into Princess Hejia
صادفت الأميرة هيجيا
in the garden.
في الحديقة.
She was quick and smart enough to cause a distraction.
كانت سريعة وذكية بما يكفي لإلهاء.
That was how I got away.
هكذا أفلتت.
If she'd go that far for you,
إذا ذهبت إلى هذا الحد من أجلك ،
it means she still cares about you.
هذا يعني أنها لا تزال تهتم بك.
Ziyi is...
زيي هو ...
Anyway,
على أي حال،
she doesn't open up to me as you do.
هي لا تفتح لي كما تفعل أنت.
Lingsu, what's wrong?
Lingsu ، ما هو الخطأ؟
It's nothing. I just need some rest.
إنه لاشيء.  أنا فقط بحاجة لبعض الراحة.
Brother Hu.
الأخ هو.
Sister Ma finished her medicine.
أنهت الأخت ما علاجها.
Fei, you should check on her.
فاي ، يجب عليك الاطمئنان عليها.
I'll tend to her now.
سأعتني بها الآن.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Yes.
نعم.
(He's been so honest with me.)
(لقد كان صادقًا معي).
(He doesn't keep any secrets from me.)
(لا يخفي عني أي أسرار).
(Should I tell him my condition)
(هل أخبره بحالتي)
(to truly open up to him?)
(للانفتاح عليه حقًا؟)
Master.
يتقن.
The capital is a large city.
العاصمة مدينة كبيرة.
Where do I find him?
أين أجده؟
I know where he is.
أعرف أين هو.
Feihong has done her investigation.
قامت Feihong بتحقيقها.
Hu Fei now leads the Huaquan Sect.
يقود Hu Fei الآن طائفة Huaquan.
He is their new leader.
هو قائدهم الجديد.
Go at night in disguise.
اذهب ليلا متخفيا.
Find a way to bring the boys back.
ابحث عن طريقة لإعادة الأولاد.
(Huaquan Sect)
(طائفة هوا تشيوان)
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
There is a girl outside
هناك فتاة في الخارج
who wants to see the chief.
من يريد أن يرى الرئيس.
What girl?
ما فتاة؟
No idea.
لا أعلم.
She said she knew the chief.
قالت إنها تعرف الرئيس.
Her surname is Yuan.
لقبها هو يوان.
Keep watch outside the room.
استمر في المراقبة خارج الغرفة.
I'll talk with her.
سأتحدث معها.
Go.
يذهب.
How did you find us here?
كيف وجدتنا هنا؟
You must be Xiaomei.
يجب أن تكون Xiaomei.
We're not that close.
نحن لسنا بهذا القرب.
So, what do you want this time?
اذا ماذا تريد هذه المرة؟
Who else is here with you?
من غيرك هنا معك؟
I came alone.
جئت وحدي.
I'm here for an important matter.
أنا هنا لأمر مهم.
If there's anything, talk to me.
إذا كان هناك أي شيء ، تحدث معي.
Brother Hu is busy.
الأخ هو مشغول.
Xiaomei, don't be rude.
Xiaomei ، لا تكن وقحًا.
Sister Cheng.
الأخت تشنغ.
Who knows how she finds us?
من يعرف كيف تجدنا؟
She must have come
لا بد أنها جاءت
with ill intentions.
بنوايا سيئة.
What if she sees Brother Hu...
ماذا لو رأت الأخ هو ...
Gentlemen, you may return to your room now.
أيها السادة ، يمكنكم العودة إلى غرفتكم الآن.
Alright, I know what to do.
حسنًا ، أعرف ماذا أفعل.
Keep watch outside the room.
استمر في المراقبة خارج الغرفة.
Keep your eyes on Brother Hu.
ابق عينيك على الأخ هو.
Young Lady Yuan.
سيدة شابة يوان.
My brother is treating a patient with his qi.
أخي يعالج مريضًا باستخدامه.
Please wait in my room.
من فضلك انتظر في غرفتي.
Red candles moved, peach tree leaves danced.
تحركت الشموع الحمراء ، ورقصت أوراق شجرة الخوخ.
Violet dress waved, berry tree branches reached.
لوح الثوب البنفسجي ، ووصلت أغصان شجر التوت.
Bai Juyi's poem
قصيدة باي جوي
seems to reflect our circumstances.
يبدو أنه يعكس ظروفنا.
Please have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
To your health.
لصحتك.
Thank you for your assistance last night.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك الليلة الماضية.
Assistance?
مساعدة؟
There is no need to hide.
ليست هناك حاجة للاختباء.
You provided cover for our carriage
لقد قدمت غطاءً لعربتنا
and used hidden weapons
واستخدموا أسلحة مخفية
to stop the soldiers.
لوقف الجنود.
Did you come up with that plan?
هل توصلت إلى هذه الخطة؟
Hu Fei is rash and imprudent,
Hu Fei هو طفح جلدي وغير حكيم ،
he rarely thinks about the consequences.
نادرا ما يفكر في العواقب.
You seem to know him very well.
يبدو أنك تعرفه جيدًا.
Compared to you,
مقارنة لك،
he and I are only acquaintances.
هو وأنا معارف فقط.
You are too humble.
أنت متواضع جدا.
To save my brother,
لإنقاذ أخي ،
you climbed up the ten thousand of stairs
صعدت عشرة آلاف درج
to get the medicine from Weituo Sect.
للحصول على الدواء من Weituo Sect.
He often talks
كثيرا ما يتحدث
and feels grateful about it.
ويشعر بالامتنان حيال ذلك.
The bond you share with him
الرابطة التي تشاركها معه
is much deeper than just
أعمق بكثير من مجرد
mere acquaintances.
مجرد معارف.
It seems...
يبدو...
he's told you
قال لك
everything about me.
كل شيء عني.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
He is honest and candid.
إنه أمين وصريح.
He tells me everything.
يقول لي كل شيء.
But to him,
لكن بالنسبة له ،
you're the one he cannot forget.
أنت الشخص الذي لا يستطيع نسيانه.
He remembers every bit of kindness.
يتذكر كل جزء من اللطف.
When he's shown kindness,
عندما أظهر اللطف ،
he'll want to repay them tenfold.
سيرغب في سدادها بعشرة أضعاف.
But he's not a good judge of character
لكنه ليس قاضيًا جيدًا في الشخصية
and is too sentimental
وهو عاطفي جدا
to tell the good from evil.
لتمييز الخير من الشر.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
But fortunately,
لكن لحسن الحظ،
he has a brilliant mind like you
لديه عقل لامع مثلك
by his side all the time.
إلى جانبه في كل وقت.
He will make it through any danger.
سوف يجتاز أي خطر.
I'm flattered.
أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
I'm not as brilliant as you think.
أنا لست بارعًا كما تعتقد.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I could have given him answers
كان بإمكاني إعطائه إجابات
and learned what had happened at the Guanyin temple.
وعلمت ما حدث في معبد قوانيين.
Do you want to know why?
هل تريد أن تعرف لماذا؟
Very well.
ممتاز.
I'll tell you everything.
سأخبرك بكل شيء.
That means...
هذا يعني...
Feng Tiannan is your...
فنغ تيانان هو ...
Indeed.
في الواقع.
But I will never accept it.
لكنني لن أقبله أبدًا.
Hu Fei has hated him for months,
لقد كرهه هو في لأشهر ،
but I've hated him my entire life.
لكني كرهته طوال حياتي.
You should tell him about your past.
يجب أن تخبره عن ماضيك.
That will clear all the doubts.
هذا سوف يزيل كل الشكوك.
But it doesn't change the fact
لكنها لا تغير الحقيقة
I am the daughter of that scoundrel.
أنا ابنة هذا الوغد.
I despise who I am.
أنا أحتقر من أنا.
I hate that Feng Tiannan's blood flows in me.
أكره أن دم فنغ تيانان يتدفق في داخلي.
So promise,
لذا وعد ،
keep this secret for me.
احتفظ بهذا السر لي.
Tell no one.
لا تخبر احدا.
But it's too sad
لكن هذا محزن للغاية
for you two to part way
لكما اثنان لجزء من الطريق
because of this.
و لهذا.
It's our fate.
إنه قدرنا.
He and I
هو و انا
are not meant to be.
ليس من المفترض أن يكون.
I'm more grateful for my upbringing.
أنا ممتن أكثر لتربيتي.
I was raised by my master.
لقد نشأت من قبل سيدي.
I took an oath
أقسمت
to follow her and practice Buddhist teachings
لاتباعها وممارسة التعاليم البوذية
to repay her kindness.
لرد لطفها.
I am a member of the Tianshan Sect.
أنا عضو في طائفة تيانشان.
I must not get involved with him again.
يجب ألا أتدخل معه مرة أخرى.
I went to the Weituo Sect for him
ذهبت إلى طائفة Weituo من أجله
to return the favor.
لرد الجميل.
I'm not as selfless as you.
أنا لست نكران الذات مثلك.
Young Lady Cheng.
السيدة الشابة تشنغ.
You are kind and smart.
انت لطيف وذكي
You put him before everything.
أنت تضعه قبل كل شيء.
I can tell
استطيع أن أقول
your love for him is true.
حبك له حقيقي.
From what I've seen,
مما رأيت
you and Hu Fei
أنت و Hu Fei
are a match made in heaven.
هي مباراة صنعت في الجنة.
May you stay happy and grow old together.
نرجو أن تظل سعيدًا وتتقدم في العمر معًا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Do not be concerned.
لا تقلق.
It's an old ailment.
إنه مرض قديم.
You wished we could grow old together,
لقد تمنيت أن نكبر معًا ،
but I doubt
لكني أشك
I'll live that long.
سأعيش كل هذا الوقت.
As I told you,
كما أخبرتك ،
Hu Fei tells me everything.
يخبرني Hu Fei بكل شيء.
He never keeps secrets.
لا يحتفظ بالأسرار أبدًا.
But I've been keeping a secret.
لكني كنت أبقى سرا.
(I was born in Miaojiang.)
(ولدت في مياوجيانغ.)
(A venomous poison ailed me.)
(لقد أزعجني سم سام.)
(My master cured me.)
(شفاني سيدي.)
(To save me,)
(لإنقاذي ،)
(my master had tried all sorts of formulae)
(جرب سيدي جميع أنواع الصيغ)
(until I was cured of that poison.)
(حتى شفيت من هذا السم).
(But my body was too weak.)
(لكن جسدي كان ضعيفًا جدًا).
(The poison had lingered too long.)
(لقد ظل السم طويلا جدا).
(It took a toll on me.)
(لقد أثر ذلك عليّ).
(To extend my lifespan,)
(لإطالة عمري ،)
(my master spent many years)
(قضى سيدي سنوات عديدة)
(to formulate the Nine Times Vitality Restoring Pill.)
(لصياغة حبة Nine Times Vitality Restoring.)
Brother Hu's love for you aside,
بغض النظر عن حب الأخ هو لك ،
I couldn't answer his love
لم أستطع الرد على حبه
even if I wanted to.
حتى لو أردت ذلك.
It's hard to make the pills I need.
من الصعب صنع الحبوب التي أحتاجها.
The stock is running low.
المخزون ينخفض.
I used to live among herbs in the Medicine King Valley.
كنت أعيش بين الأعشاب في وادي ملك الطب.
I didn't need many pills, for my life was peaceful.
لم أكن بحاجة إلى الكثير من الحبوب ، لأن حياتي كانت سلمية.
I only needed them after I left.
كنت بحاجة إليهم فقط بعد أن غادرت.
I thought I'd never leave the valley,
ظننت أنني لن أغادر الوادي أبدًا ،
but who knows?
لكن من يعلم؟
It's been months since I left.
لقد مرت شهور منذ أن غادرت.
You're running low on pills.
حبوب منع الحمل تنفد.
How will you cope with it?
كيف ستتعامل معها؟
Sister Ma will be well
الأخت ما ستكون على ما يرام
after a day or two.
بعد يوم أو يومين.
After she's recovered,
بعد أن تعافت ،
I shall return.
سأعود.
What still worries me is my brother.
ما يزال يقلقني هو أخي.
He's always seen me as his sister,
لطالما رآني أخته ،
and not his lover.
وليس عشيقته.
Besides,
بجانب،
I'm sick
أنا مريض
and will die soon.
وسيموت قريبا.
Love is a luxury to me.
الحب ترف بالنسبة لي.
I know how deeply he loves you.
أنا أعلم كم هو حبك بعمق.
Please, reconsider.
يرجى إعادة النظر.
Your master cares about you.
سيدك يهتم بك.
She will be considerate
سوف تكون مراعية
and give you her blessing.
وأعطيكم مباركتها.
Enough about that.
كفى عن ذلك.
Back to business.
العودة إلى العمل.
I didn't come here for Hu Fei.
أنا لم آتي إلى هنا من أجل Hu Fei.
I'm here for the boys.
أنا هنا من أجل الأولاد.
I'm from the Red Flower Club.
أنا من نادي ريد فلاور.
President Chen learned the Imperial Court would hold
علم الرئيس تشين أن البلاط الإمبراطوري سيصمد
Sect Leaders Gathering in the capital
تجمع قادة الطوائف في العاصمة
and the conspiracy around it.
والمؤامرة حولها.
It's our plan to sabotage it.
إنها خطتنا لتخريبها.
But the top executives of the Red Flower Club
لكن كبار المديرين التنفيذيين في نادي الزهرة الحمراء
are all wanted by the Imperial Court.
مطلوبون جميعًا من قبل المحكمة الإمبراطورية.
It's impossible for them to come and go to the city.
من المستحيل عليهم المجيء والذهاب إلى المدينة.
They wrote Hero Miao a letter to request his help.
لقد كتبوا رسالة إلى Hero Miao لطلب مساعدته.
But something unexpected happened.
لكن حدث شيء غير متوقع.
My master was ordered
أمر سيدي
to come here,
لتأتي إلى هنا،
and went through great effort
وبذل جهد كبير
to earn Official Fu's trust.
لكسب ثقة Official Fu.
But my mistake cost them the boys.
لكن خطئي كلفهم الأولاد.
Right now,
فى الحال،
I must bring the boys back
يجب أن أعيد الأولاد
to regain their trust.
لاستعادة ثقتهم.
Why didn't the Red Flower Club ask Brother Hu for help?
لماذا لم يطلب نادي الزهرة الحمراء المساعدة من Brother Hu؟
This mission
هذه المهمة
is full of great risks.
مليء بالمخاطر الكبيرة.
One must endure
يجب على المرء أن يتحمل
for the greater good.
من أجل الصالح العام.
Hu Fei is too candid
Hu Fei صريح للغاية
and never bows to evil.
ولا تنحني للشر أبدًا.
Perhaps
ربما
this isn't a job for him.
هذه ليست وظيفة بالنسبة له.
Sister Yuan.
الأخت يوان.
I apologize to you.
انا اعتذر لك.
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
the matter was so complicated.
كانت المسألة معقدة للغاية.
I was wrong about you.
كنت مخطئا فيك.
I thought you were irrational,
اعتقدت أنك غير عقلاني ،
that you came with an ill intention.
أنك أتيت بنية سيئة.
I lit poison candles as a precaution.
أشعلت الشموع السامة كإجراء احترازي.
Given all the doubts have been cleared,
بالنظر إلى كل الشكوك قد أزيلت ،
I must give you the antidote
يجب أن أعطيك الترياق
as apology.
كاعتذار.
As expected from the Medicine King Sect.
كما هو متوقع من طائفة الملك الطب.
Your poisons come in all forms.
السموم الخاصة بك تأتي في جميع الأشكال.
I've finally seen it
لقد رأيته أخيرًا
with my eyes.
بعيني.
My request for you
طلبي لك
was indeed inappropriate.
كان غير مناسب بالفعل.
If I'm to be poisoned,
إذا تعرضت للتسمم ،
I'll gladly accept it.
سأقبله بكل سرور.
However,
لكن،
how do I convince Hu Fei?
كيف أقنع Hu Fei؟
You need not worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
I'll help.
انا سوف اساعد.
Sister Cheng.
الأخت تشنغ.
Where are you taking the boys?
إلى أين تأخذ الأولاد؟
Xiaomei, step aside.
Xiaomei ، تنحى جانبا.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Keep it down.
احتفظ به.
Do not let Brother Hu hear you.
لا تدع الأخ هو يسمعك.
No.
رقم.
That woman is working for Fu Kang'an.
تلك المرأة تعمل لصالح فو كانغان.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
So what is the truth?
اذا، فما هي الحقيقة؟
Explain yourself.
عرف نفسك.
What if Sister Ma asks for her children?
ماذا لو طلبت الأخت ما أطفالها؟
How will you explain this to Brother Hu?
كيف تشرح هذا للأخ هو؟
Ziyi?
ما هم؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Brother Hu.
الأخ هو.
She is taking the kids.
هي تأخذ الأطفال.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Fei,
فاي ،
let Young Lady Yuan take the boys.
دع السيدة "يوان" تأخذ الأولاد.
She will bring them back after the gathering.
سوف تعيدهم بعد التجمع.
No.
رقم.
Give me the boys.
أعطني الأولاد.
But I promised her.
لكني وعدتها.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Hu Fei.
هو فيي.
This is urgent.
هذا عاجل.
We don't have time to explain.
ليس لدينا وقت للشرح.
I will return the boys in five days.
سأعيد الأولاد في خمسة أيام.
If I break the promise...
إذا حنثت بالوعد ...
You may cut me down.
قد تقطعني.
This lady here is Uncle Hu's friend.
هذه السيدة هنا صديقة العم هو.
You must listen to her.
يجب أن تستمع إليها.
Remember to help her out.
تذكر أن تساعدها.
Go on.
تابع.
Fei, don't worry.
فاي ، لا تقلق.
Sister Yuan won't break her promise.
لن تخلف الأخت يوان وعدها.
Lingsu.
Lingsu.
How did you two become so close over the night?
كيف أصبحتا قريبين جدا خلال الليل؟
Why do you defend her?
لماذا تدافع عنها؟
What did Ziyi tell you?
ماذا قال لك زيي؟
I promise her
أعدها
I'd say nothing.
لن أقول شيئا.
Not even to me?
ولا حتى لي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Especially you.
خصوصا أنت.
I can't disclose anything.
لا أستطيع الكشف عن أي شيء.
But...
ولكن...
Fei.
فاي.
Please don't make it hard for me.
من فضلك لا تجعل من الصعب علي.
Just remember that
فقط تذكر هذا
everyone has their unspeakable reasons.
لكل شخص أسبابه التي لا توصف.
It's the same for Sister Yuan.
إنه نفس الشيء بالنسبة للأخت يوان.
My son Yiming has found the woman.
وجد ابني Yiming المرأة.
We'll wreak havoc tonight.
سوف نعيث فسادا الليلة.
With the two of us working together,
مع عملنا معًا ،
we can accomplish anything.
يمكننا تحقيق أي شيء.
Father, Uncle Tang.
الأب ، العم تانغ.
If we keep watch here tonight,
إذا واصلنا المشاهدة هنا الليلة ،
we will catch her.
سوف نقبض عليها.
Well done.
أحسنت.
If we catch her,
إذا أمسكناها ،
it's a great feat.
إنه عمل رائع.
Everyone, stay alert!
الجميع ، ابقوا يقظين!
Tonight is the night you make a name for yourselves!
الليلة هي الليلة التي تصنعون فيها اسمًا لأنفسكم!
Yes!
نعم!
Ziyi.
هم انهم.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you upset I didn't tell you about Hu Fei?
هل أنت مستاء لأنني لم أخبرك عن Hu Fei؟
I didn't mean to.
لم أقصد ذلك.
Master wouldn't let me tell you.
سيد لا يسمح لي أن أخبرك.
I can still make it up to you.
لا يزال بإمكاني أن أعوضك.
As soon as I learn anything about him,
بمجرد أن أعرف أي شيء عنه ،
you'll be the first to know.
ستكون أول من يعلم.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
Do you want to know
هل تريد أن تعرف
who the girl by his side is?
من هي الفتاة التي بجانبه؟
Don't worry, leave it to me.
لا تقلق ، اتركه لي.
I'll find everything to know about her.
سأجد كل شيء لأعرفه عنها.
Enough.
كافية.
It's not that.
انها ليست التي.
It's not my fault?
ليس خطئي؟
Is it because of Hu Fei?
هل هو بسبب Hu Fei؟
By the way, I forgot to ask.
بالمناسبة ، لقد نسيت أن أسأل.
How did you explain to him
كيف شرحت له
when you went to their manor?
عندما ذهبت إلى قصرهم؟
He really trusts you.
إنه يثق بك حقًا.
You asked for the kids and he just handed them over.
لقد طلبت الأطفال وسلمهم للتو.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Focus on driving.
ركز على القيادة.
Pull over.
قف بجانب الطريق.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
You are working together.
أنتم تعملون معًا.
Chief Feng.
رئيس فنغ.
It's our lucky night.
إنها ليلتنا المحظوظة.
Take them down!
خذهم الى الائسفل!
Hide inside.
اختبئ بالداخل.
Yiming!
ييمينغ!
Ziyi, keep the boys safe.
زيي ، حافظ على سلامة الأولاد.
Go!
يذهب!
Yiming!
ييمينغ!
Catch her!
الحق بها!
Feihong.
فيهونغ.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
My son...
ابني...
My son!
ابني!
Master.
يتقن.
Feihong has been captured.
تم القبض على Feihong.
Tie her up!
ربط لها حتى!
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Who is she?
من هي؟
Where did you get her?
من اين حصلت عليها؟
Officers.
الضباط.
This woman
هذه المرأة
is responsible for kidnapping the little princes.
هو المسؤول عن اختطاف الأمراء الصغار.
She's the culprit.
إنها الجاني.
Stay still!
اثبت مكانك!
Great. Wonderful.
رائعة.  رائع.
Brother Tang, Chief Feng, well done.
الأخ تانغ ، الزعيم فنغ ، أحسنت.
I'll take her to Official Fu now.
سآخذها إلى Official Fu الآن.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Wait.
انتظر.
Well...
نحن سوف...
After the last attack,
بعد الهجوم الأخير ،
Official Fu scolded me and blamed me for everything.
وبخني المسؤول فو ولومني على كل شيء.
If she gets away,
إذا ابتعدت ،
or anything goes wrong,
أو حدث خطأ ما ،
I could lose everything.
يمكن أن أفقد كل شيء.
What is the meaning of this?
ما معنى هذا؟
Don't you trust the guards?
ألا تثق بالحراس؟
No, misunderstood.
لا ، أسيء فهمه.
My son died because of her!
مات ابني بسببها!
I must take her to Official Fu personally.
يجب أن آخذها إلى Official Fu شخصيًا.
In that case...
في هذه الحالة...
Come in.
ادخل.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Move.
يتحرك.
Tiejiao.
تيجياو.
If that girl is connected to Hu Fei,
إذا كانت تلك الفتاة مرتبطة بـ Hu Fei ،
we'll be in danger.
سنكون في خطر.
Don't be so paranoid.
لا تكن بجنون العظمة.
Greetings, sirs.
تحياتي يا سادة.
You did great, brothers.
لقد أبليت بلاءً حسنًا ، أيها الإخوة.
Yes.
نعم.
Brothers,
الإخوة،
the girl we met
الفتاة التي التقينا بها
at Brother Hu's place
في مكان Brother Hu
wasn't her.
لم تكن هي.
Don't be silly.
لا تكن سخيفا.
They are clearly working together.
من الواضح أنهم يعملون معًا.
If she tells Official Fu
إذا أخبرت الرسمية فو
we'd helped Hu Fei,
كنا قد ساعدنا Hu Fei ،
we'll be in deep trouble.
سنكون في ورطة عميقة.
We can't trust her to keep the secret.
لا يمكننا الوثوق بها للحفاظ على السر.
So, what do we do now, Tiejiao?
لذا ، ماذا سنفعل الآن يا تيجياو؟
I noticed the look in her eyes.
لقد لاحظت النظرة في عينيها.
When she saw us,
عندما رأتنا ،
we were strangers to her.
كنا غرباء عنها.
Even if she was working for Hu Fei,
حتى لو كانت تعمل لدى Hu Fei ،
she couldn't testify against us.
لم تستطع الشهادة ضدنا.
But what if...
ولكن ماذا لو...
Don't be so paranoid.
لا تكن بجنون العظمة.
I've thought it through.
لقد فكرت في الأمر.
Each of us contacted Hu Fei individually.
اتصل كل منا بـ Hu Fei بشكل فردي.
As long as Hu Fei is safe,
طالما أن Hu Fei آمن ،
we are safe.
نحن بمأمن.
Go.
يذهب.
Let's meet Official Fu.
دعونا نلتقي الرسمية فو.
Official Fu.
الرسمية فو.
Chief Tang and Chief Feng want to see you.
الزعيم تانغ والرئيس فنغ يريدون رؤيتك.
It's about the boys.
يتعلق الأمر بالأولاد.
Bring them here.
أحضرهم هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
Your Honor.
فخامتك.
Where are the kids?
اين الاطفال
I apologize.
أنا أعتذر.
I saw the boys,
رأيت الأولاد ،
but I couldn't save them.
لكنني لم أستطع حفظهم.
I only managed to catch this woman.
تمكنت فقط من الإمساك بهذه المرأة.
Kneel!
اركع!
She is the All-Knowing Nun's disciple.
هي تلميذة الراهبة العارفين.
Your Honor.
فخامتك.
My son Yiming died trying to save
مات ابني ييمينغ وهو يحاول الإنقاذ
the two little princes.
الأميران الصغار.
My son deserves justice!
ابني يستحق العدل!
Your Honor, please send the order
معالي الوزير ، يرجى إرسال الطلب
to raid chief accommodation
لمداهمة سكن كبير
and arrest the Nun
واعتقال الراهبة
and her other disciple.
وتلميذها الآخر.
Guards!
حراس!
My little princes, don't be afraid.
أمرائي الصغار ، لا تخافوا.
Protect Official Fu!
حماية الرسمية فو!
Come to me, my sons.
تعالوا إليّ يا أبنائي.
Let me take a look at you.
دعني ألقي نظرة عليك.
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
No.
رقم.
Amitabha.
أميتابها.
The two boys were rescued
تم انقاذ الصبيان
and fortunate to survive the attack.
ومن حسن حظنا أن نجا من الهجوم.
Your Honor.
فخامتك.
Take them to the room.
خذهم إلى الغرفة.
Take good care of them.
تأخذ الرعاية الجيدة منها.
Yes.
نعم.
Venerable.
جليل.
Please stay.
من فضلك إبقى.
I have something to say.
لدي شيء لأقوله.
♪Life passes by♪
الحياة تمر
♪In the blink of an eye♪
في غمضة عين ♪
♪My heart is tied up♪
قلبي مقيد ♪
♪By the unintentional worry♪
من القلق غير المتعمد ♪
♪What does the future hold?♪
ماذا يخبئ المستقبل؟
♪Hopefully, all wishes will be fulfilled♪
♪ آمل أن تتحقق كل الأمنيات ♪
♪What brings us together?♪
ما الذي يجمعنا؟
♪Why are we going separate ways?♪
♪ لماذا نذهب بطرق منفصلة؟
♪I can never express love and hate in words♪
♪ لا أستطيع أبدًا التعبير عن الحب والكراهية بالكلمات
♪Going through all the winters in our lives♪
نمر بكل فصول الشتاء في حياتنا
♪Disposing of the unfulfilled wishes♪
التخلص من الرغبات التي لم تتحقق
♪And keeping them all to myself♪
وأحتفظ بها جميعًا لنفسي
♪Love only lasts so briefly♪
الحب لا يدوم إلا لفترة وجيزة ♪
♪Who do I waste my time for?♪
♪ لمن أضيع وقتي؟ ♪
♪Life is already full of debts♪
الحياة مليئة بالفعل بالديون
♪So let's not dwell on the little time we have♪
♪ لذلك دعونا لا نتحدث عن القليل من الوقت الذي لدينا